JARUWAT POHONG

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

CONTACT

085-675-7345 contact@jaruwat.dev https://jaruwat.dev github.com/l3lackMegas

EDUCATION

Bangkok University

2019 - 2023

School of Information

Technology and Innovation

Computer Science

Language

Thai (Native) English (CEFR B2)

Portfolio

jaruwat.dev/portfolio



PROFILE

I have 3 years of working experience as a Software Developer. However, I have been learning and gaining experience in software development for many years prior to this. I have consistently studied, understood, and developed personal projects throughout my journey. This has provided me with a strong understanding of technology trends over the past 10 years, enabling me to effectively apply my experience in my work.

EXPERIENCE

Orisma Technology

2022 - Present

Develop products for company and their customers.

- Designing project structures and developing core system.
- Using Flutter, React Native, and Vue Native to develop mobile application.
- Maintained legacy codebases to ensure continued usability and support future development.

FPSMember Website

2020 - 2022 (Freelance)

This project was commissioned by FPSThailand to allow their Twitch members to participate in random prize giveaways from their favorite streamers.

- I was involved in the design and development of the frontend and the prize giveaway algorithm.
- Written with basic HTML, CSS and JS (with jQuery)
- Maintenance while providing service and develop features according to each phase in the time frame.

SKILL

Programing Language: TS, JS, Dart, C#, Python, PHP, Lua, SQL, Golana

Framework: Flutter, React Native, ElysiaJS, Next.js, Electron

Libraries: React.js, Drift, Framer Motion

Other: Drizzle ORM, Git, Docker, MongoDB, SCSS, LESS